<SageTVPlugin>
  <Name>Canadian Channel Logo Pack</Name>
  <Identifier>canadianchannellogopack</Identifier>
  <Description>A complete collection of hi-res channel logos (600x300 JPG's) cleaned up and scaled with Photoshop on black backgrounds for the following areas,

BELL EAST
BELL WEST
TELUS TV CALGARY
TELUS TV SAT BC AB
BELL TV CABLE TORONTO
SHAW CALGARY DIGITAL
SHAW DIRECT EAST (Starchoice)
SHAW DIRECT WEST (Starchoice)
SHAW NANAIMO DIGITAL
SHAW VANCOUVER DIGITAL
SHAW VICTORIA DIGITAL
SHAW EDMONTON DIGITAL
SHAW SASKATOON DIGITAL
SHAW WINNEPEG DIGITAL
SHAW KELOWNA DIGITAL
SHAW PRINCEGEORGE DIGITAL
ROGERS TORONTO DIGITAL
ROGERS KITCHENER GRAND RIVER DIGITAL
ROGERS BRAMPTON DIGITAL
ROGERS MISS REXDALE DIGITAL
ROGERS OTTAWA DIGITAL
COGECO OAKVILLE DIGITAL
VIDEOTRON MONTREAL
VIDEOTRON QUEBEC CITY DIGITAL

This pack contains 960 logos named to work with the above providers and lineups verifed on Zap2it within the last few weeks.  All channels are included and I hope by picking the lineups above I will have created enough overlap for the other areas not included.  You should be able to just install this set and all channels should show up without renaming the files etc.  There is a chance that if you are not in one of the above areas that the odd channel might be missing (local or specialty etc) and you will have to source the missing channel image.

The download is about 20MB in size.

I will be converting the whole set to transparent logos as I have time in the near future.

Disclaimer - I have done my best to research (Google, Wikipedia, Lyngsat) and choose the correct logo for each channel but there is a chance that there may be some logos that won't match so please let me know and I will correct.  International logos were a bit of a problem as most channels didn't have a hi res image availible but I think they turned out ok most of the time.

</Description>
  <Author>jorton</Author>
  <CreationDate>2010-07-08</CreationDate>
  <ModificationDate>2010.07.08</ModificationDate>
  <Version>1.0</Version>
  <Desktop>false</Desktop>
  <PluginType>Images</PluginType>
  <Package>
    <PackageType>ChannelLogo</PackageType>
   <Location>http://storage.googleapis.com/google-code-archive-downloads/v2/code.google.com/jorton/ALLCANADA.zip</Location>
    <MD5>07380a9d7c066a5b145e36e55951d165</MD5>
  </Package>
</SageTVPlugin>
