<SageTVPlugin>

   <Name>PlayOn For SageTV</Name>

   <Identifier>PlayOnSTVI</Identifier>

   <Description><![CDATA[Plugin for viewing PlayOn content in SageTV]]></Description>

   <Author>evilpenguin</Author>

   <CreationDate>2010.06.01</CreationDate>

   <ModificationDate>2012.11.25</ModificationDate>

   <Version>1.80</Version>

   <Desktop>false</Desktop>

   <OS>Windows</OS>

   <Screenshot title="Main Menu"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=12281&d=1300743633]]></Screenshot>

   <Screenshot title="Menu Settings"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=12286&d=1300744452]]></Screenshot>

   <Screenshot title="ABC Shows"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=12280&d=1300743603]]></Screenshot>

   <Screenshot title="Diamond TV"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=12283&d=1300743647]]></Screenshot>

   <Screenshot title="Diamond TV Filtering"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=12285&d=1300744448]]></Screenshot>

   <Screenshot title="Diamond 360 Flow"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=12279&d=1300743599]]></Screenshot>

   <Screenshot title="Diamond List Flow"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=12284&d=1300744440]]></Screenshot>

   <Webpage><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/showthread.php?t=54756]]></Webpage>

   <ReleaseNotes>

     * v1.80

     * UPnPBrowser: Fixed Netflix TV show queue importer

     * UPnPBrowser: Added UPnPBrowser.jump to customize folders to skip over via RegEx

     * UPnPBrowser: Added UPnPBrowser.images to specify custom images for PlayOn Folders

     * UPnPBrowser: Added UPnPBrowser.regex to specify the queue importer sraping RegEx's for fixing things like the Netflix issue w/o a full plugin update

     * UPnPBrowser: Made it so custom paths can contain multiple PlayOn folders for combining multiple menus together

     * UPnPBrowser: Added the ability to force a folder name and description from within a custom path

     * UPnPBrowser: If no custom image exists for path, just try finding a Hulu one since they have a lot of images for other shows

     * UPnPBrowser: Added configurable length for commercials.

     * STVi: Updated STVi to include updated presets

     * STVi: Included some basic support for Gemstone ADM, see forum post for details.



     * v1.60

     * UPnPBrowser: Fixed issue where some charactors were crashing scraper

     * UPnPBrowser: Updated Queue Importer to work with new Netflix TV format

     * UPnPBrowser: Fixed issue with Queue Importer files being overwritten every night

     * UPnPBrowser: Worked around issue with Queue Importer files with special charactors



     * v1.55

     * STVi: Accidentally modified a theme attribute that let the main menu wrap vertially



     * v1.54

     * STVi: Moved PlayOn to its own menu.  Didn't realize it would fit before.



     * v1.53

     * UPnPBrowser: Worked around annoying Anti-virus false positive issue.



     * v1.52

     * STVi: Added ability to keep PlayOn in Online

     * STVi: Fixed options



     * v1.51

     * NOTE: Removed Linux support.  Not sure what the problem is and I don't have the time to figure out why it doesn't work.

     * STVi: Added additional channels to the main menu

     * STVi: Added setup menu for enabling disabling most channels

     * STVi: Added shortcut to Queue Importer settings

     * STVi: Cleaned up some unused code

     * JAR: Added custom metadata properties for Queue Importer (Copyright, COmment)

     * JAR: Added multiple different ways to import/clean content

     * JAR: Tweaked defaults settings to disable automatic importing by default

     * JAR: Added a STV utilites JAR for devs who want to support PlayOn content, see thread for more info

     * UPnPBrowser: Added AtomicParsley for tagging dummy videos with queue importer info

     * UPnPBrowser: Added video tag for diferentiating between Hulu/Netflix content

     * UPnPBrowser: Stopped putting titles in file names to work around some annoying UTF8 issues

     * UPnPBrowser: Fixed bug where PlayOn Queue Importer would import too many videos

     * UPnPBrowser: Cleaning up a bunch of UTF-8 issues



     * v1.4

     * STVi: Fixed meathod of entring Online Servies menu (Thanks Andy!)

     * STVi: Added options for configuring PlayOn Scraping

     * STVi: Added ability to playback PlayOn dummy videos properly

     * UPnPBrowser: Fixed some path issues for Linux

     * UPnPBrowser: Displaying duration on video entries

     * UPnPBrowser: Added ability to scrape PlayOn Paths and genrate dummy videos for importing into Sage

     * UPnPBrowser: Fixed accounting for commericals in shows/clips under 1 minutes



     *  v1.3

     * STVi: Fixed unique names in main menu buttons

     * STVi: Fixed linux file sepeators for launching UPnPBrowser.exe

     * STVi: Added .property files for people with SageMC

     * STVi: Added menu button for generic UPnP Browsing

     * UPnPBrowser: Made commerical allowance longer

     * UPnPBrowser: Fixed issue where finding parent folder of a folder was broken



     * v1.2

     * Fixed issue with 64-bit windows users

     * Added option to do an extra long server scan when the device isn't found

     * Invalidating .cache files if server changes

     * Added depedency on v7 STV

     * Fixed some spelling errors

   </ReleaseNotes>

   <PluginType>STVI</PluginType>

   <Dependency>

     <Plugin>UPnPBrowser</Plugin>

     <MinVersion>1.80</MinVersion>

   </Dependency>

   <Dependency>

     <STV>SageTV7</STV>

     <MinVersion>7.0.23</MinVersion>

   </Dependency>

   <Dependency>

     <Plugin>PlayOnForSageTV</Plugin>

     <MinVersion>1.51</MinVersion>

   </Dependency>

   <Dependency>

     <Plugin>PlayOnForSageTVUtilities</Plugin>

     <MinVersion>1.51</MinVersion>

   </Dependency>

   <Package>

     <PackageType>STVI</PackageType>

     <Location><![CDATA[http://storage.googleapis.com/google-code-archive-downloads/v2/code.google.com/upnp2podcast/PlayOnSTVI_v1_8.zip]]></Location>

     <MD5>11f5d5441d9a5acf382e0c73e655762c</MD5>

   </Package>

   <STVImport>PlayOn_v1_8.stvi</STVImport>

 </SageTVPlugin>
