<SageTVPlugin>

<Name>SageTV Catchup</Name>

<Identifier>sagetvcatchup</Identifier>

<Description>

<![CDATA[

Plugin to integrate UK catchup TV sources into SageTV for UK users.





Requires separate installation of get_iplayer.





Use version 2.94 or later of get_iplayer which handles the latest changes to BBC IPlayer website.

]]>



</Description>

<Author>michaeldjcox</Author>

<CreationDate>2013.04.01</CreationDate>

<ModificationDate>2015.08.19</ModificationDate>

<Version beta="false">1.0.1</Version>

<Desktop>false</Desktop>

<Dependency>

<Plugin>sagex-api</Plugin>

<MinVersion>7.0.15.0</MinVersion>

</Dependency>

<ServerOnly>true</ServerOnly>

<ResourcePath>sagetvcatchup</ResourcePath>

<Screenshot title="TopMenu"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/TopMenu.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="AirDate"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/AirDate.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="AtoZ"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/AtoZ.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Channel"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Channel.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Favourites"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Favourites.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Genre"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Genre.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="LastChance"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/LastChance.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="MostPopular"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/MostPopular.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="New"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/New.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Sources"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Sources.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Search"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Search.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Status"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Status.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Episodes"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Episodes.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Control"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Control.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="MetaData"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/MetaData.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="RecordingStatus"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/RecordingStatus.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="RecordingProgress"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/RecordingProgress.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="CatalogingStatus"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/CatalogingStatus.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="WebPage"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/WebPage.png]]></Screenshot>

<Screenshot title="Configure"><![CDATA[http://cdn.rawgit.com/michaeldjcox/sagetvcatchup/master/screenshots/Configure.png]]></Screenshot>

<PluginType>Standard</PluginType>

<Package>

<PackageType>System</PackageType>

<Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/sagetvcatchup-1.0.1-plugin.zip</Location>

<MD5>1C6EDAF78DEED79082E6D302A033264D</MD5>

<Overwrite>true</Overwrite> <!-- Defaults to true -->

</Package>

<ImplementationClass>uk.co.mdjcox.sagetv.catchup.CatchupPlugin</ImplementationClass>

<ReleaseNotes>

<![CDATA[





1.0.1 - Breakfix following BBC Iplayer website changes.





      - Require get_iplayer 2.94 and remove dependence on playlist URLS which BBC blocks access to





1.0.0 - First official release.





      - Online Services menu. Show the last air date rather than original air date in episode detail

      - Online Services menu. Cataloging status - add a count of subcategories

      - Online Services menu. Add recording progress to stop button on episode control menu

      - Online Services menu. Add "Last chance" category for soon to be removed episodes

      - Online Services menu. Add "Most popular" category based on BBC web site

      - Online Services menu. Rework "New" category to be based on availability dates.

      - Online Services menu. Only one "Air date", "New", "Favourite" etc category for all sources

      - Online Services menu. Move "Air date", "New", "Favourite" etc to the top level

      - Online Services menu. Add "Sources" categories below which IPlayer and Test go

      - Online Services menu. Add icons for some sub categories

      - Web Page: Fix issue where podcasts cannot be navigated from remote machine

      - Web Page: Duration, last air date, available and removal dates added to episode views.

      - Cataloging: extract duration and last air date from iplayer meta data

      - Cataloging: extract available and removal dates from iplayer meta data

      - Cataloging: reduce air date categories with larger time periods for much older content

      - Cataloging: Fix issue of some catalog errors accumulating across catalog runs

      - Cataloging: Only one "Air date", "New", "Favourite" etc category for all sources

      - Recording: add channel, duration, and last air date to SageTV airing meta data

      - Recording: download the episode fanart to the recording directory.

      - Recording: fix episode title so it has the SageTVs title - SeasonNr - EpisodeNr format

      - Recording: fix episode number which was being set to same value as series number

      - Recording: upload to sagetv asynchronously from the server so as to not block recording

      - Recording: fix issue where some failed recordings gets listed as still in progress

      - Test: reduce size of the test video to reduce deployment upload times





0.3.6 - Fifth beta release.





      - SageTV Plugin: Fix issue with recordingDir property being overridden with online props dir

      - SageTV Plugin: Make online video property file dir and suffix configurable

      - Cataloging: Fix issue where Iplayer programmes get into lists for the Test source





0.3.5 - Fourth beta release.





      - SageTV Plugin: Fix issue with configurability of recording commands





0.3.4 Third beta release.





      - Online services menu: fix truncation of categories due to incorrect escaping of titles

      - SageTV Plugin: Configurability of ports and timeouts and recording commands

      - Recording: Better status reporting

      - Recording: Two threads for watching and one for queued recordings

      - Recording: Configurable timeouts

      - Recording: upload to SageTV retries move of recording file

      - Recording: recording will not wait for completed file if the recording was stopped or failed

      - Recording: get_iplayer command line is now configurable

      - Recording: remove use of relative path to recording dir

      - General: RMI services made to survive suspend/resume of host





0.3.3 Second beta release.





      Online services menu:





      - Recording and catalog status moved down a level as SageTV caches at top level

      - Reverse order sorting of categories and episodes by orig air date

      - Added a search podcast to allow programme search from SageTV

      - Moved show icons from episode to programme level for better meta-data visibility

      - Improved visibility of meta-data at episode level

      - Added a "New" category for programmes added since the last catalog

      - Added a "Favourite" category for programmes which are also SageTV favourites

      - Added recording status messages to recordings podcast including percent done

      - Added grouping of recordings by outcome e.g. in progress, failed, completed

      - Made improvements to catalog status reporting including time taken to catalog

      - Catalog errors are now grouped by message





      Recording:





      - Add "Watch and Keep mode" as SageTV only lets you record if fully downloaded.

      - Made recording and streaming much more resilient to different outcomes





      SageTV plugin:





      - Add enable/disable of individual sources in plugin configuration screen.

      - Allow catchup server port and recording directory to be configured from SageTV





      Cataloging:





      - Reduce cataloging time to 10 mins - previously took hours

      - Remove the catchup server host and port from podcast URLs from the catalog

      - Add a catalog start hour so cataloging starts at a set hour of day and occurs every X hours

      - Only start cataloging on startup if the catalog is sparse otherwise wait for scheduled time

      - Deal with duplicate programme entries in iplayer

      - Made catalog downloads interruptable so that cataloging can be more quickly terminated

      - Made catalog downloads retry on failure





      Web page:





      - Add Type column to category web page

      - Add Type column to programmes web page

      - Add error summary to catalog error web page

      - Control links in web server home page redirect back to home page

      - Home page now shows active thread count and heap stats

      - Home page now shows growing size of catalog in progress and size of last catalog





      General:





      - Moved the catchup server to its own JVM to limit the plugins impact on SageTV classpath

      - Set up RMI servers in plugin and the now separate server for better control and feedback

      - Add seed properties for 32bit windows e.g. windows XP

      - Increased maximum heap size to 500Mb





      Media sources:





      - Fix Demand5 meta data (but demand5 no longer works possible due to encryption)

      - Fix Iplayer series and episode number parsing errors





0.2.7 First beta release.





      - Contains Iplayer catalog, watch and record to TV recordings

]]>





</ReleaseNotes>

</SageTVPlugin>
