<SageTVPlugin>
<Name>Web Feed Encoder (WFE)</Name>
<Identifier>wfe</Identifier>
<Description>
<![CDATA[The webfeedencoder is a means to get web based streaming TV and radio and device output available in SageTV and its extenders as if they were regular channels.

As far as SageTV is concerned the webfeedencoder behaves like another TV tuner.

The excellent VLC media player software is used to tune to the internet TV or radio station, add video to the radio, and dump to an MPEG2 file for SageTV.

The means of tuning and detuning is completely configurable so any source of video or audio could be fed to SageTV via the webfeedencoder.

The webfeedencoder also includes an EPG grabber to harvest schedules from the web pages and other sources and update SageTVs program guide without need for an XMLTV importer.

Feeds can also be added to online services menu in SageTV.

A configuration tool is provided which allows you to:

    * Find and configure new channels and online services.
    * Test the channels and EPG harvest.
    * Perform ad-hoc EPG updates.
    * Manage your SageTV channel lineup and online services.

NOTE: You must install VLC seperately in order for the plugin to work. Version 1.0.5 is recommended.]]>
</Description>
<Author>michaeldjcox</Author>
<CreationDate>2010.07.12</CreationDate>
<ModificationDate>2010.12.10</ModificationDate>
<Version beta="false">0.9.7.400</Version>
<Desktop>false</Desktop>
<ServerOnly>true</ServerOnly>
<ResourcePath>webfeedencoder</ResourcePath>
<Webpage title="WebFeedEncoder"><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/downloads.php?do=file&id=339]]></Webpage>
<Screenshot title="Lineup management">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_lineup-10497209.jpg?ts=1263992914</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Online service management">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_onlineservices-61351583.jpg?ts=1263992916</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Channel management">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_channels-57337152.jpg?ts=1263992907</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Adding a channel">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_channeldialog-28242200.jpg?ts=1263992906</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Find podcast to add">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_findpodcast-43154103.jpg?ts=1263992911</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Find radio channels to add">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_findradio-8568694.jpg?ts=1263992911</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Find TV channels to add">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_findtv-98592665.jpg?ts=1263992911</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Now Playing Harvest">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_epgharvest-26272405.jpg?ts=1263992902</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Now Playing Harvest">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_nowplayingharvest-68893067.jpg?ts=1263992904</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Testing a channel">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_channeltest-10942287.jpg?ts=1263992910</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Testing an EPG grab">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_grabbertest-30420520.jpg?ts=1263992912</Screenshot>
<Screenshot title="Testing a now playing harvest">http://www.keepandshare.com/userpics/m/i/c/h/aeldjcox/2010-01/sm/wfe_nowplayingtest-8953325.jpg?ts=1263992915</Screenshot>
<DemoVideo title="Web Feed Encoder">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SX3vvly-OL8</DemoVideo>
<PluginType>Standard</PluginType>
<Package>
<PackageType>System</PackageType>
<Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/webfeedencoder4V7_v0_9_7.zip</Location>
<MD5>E48149642BEFAD4EA62484FE2B443FA3</MD5>
<Overwrite>true</Overwrite> <!-- Defaults to true -->
</Package>
<ImplementationClass>uk.co.mdjcox.encoderplugin.EncoderPlugin</ImplementationClass>
<ReleaseNotes>
<![CDATA[
0.9.7.400

* Created a web server within the webfeedencoder process providing a home page.
* Allow config tool to be launched from the home page accessed from any networked PC via java web start.
* Allow user guide to be accessed from the home page.
* The configtool now additionally allows video playback during channel testing in remote mode by opening a URL on the server box rather than trying to open a local file.
* New channel type: Podcast (Local) This allows creation of a locally served podcast of a web based file. In short a means to get more web content available in online services.
* SageTV V7 support.
* Allow installation and update via the SageTV V7 plugin manager.
* Added a build number to the version number scheme to facilitate more frequent updates.
* Support for multiple tuners so to allow simultaneous recording of several channels.
* New configtool file menu option to add one of the delivered sample channels to the channel list.
* Make sure we remove any additional encoder props added by SageTV on uninstall.
* On disable tidy away any partially built network encoder entries
* Add addSeriesInfoPublic method to the EPG plugin.
* Improve code for finding free encoder numbers on install.
* Make lineup send more resilient to internet connection issues.
* Fix slowness in stopping plugin when SageTV service is stopped.
* Many fixes to allow webfeedencoder operation in linux.
* Fix stop encoder button which is occasionally enabled when it should not be.
* Send logs to developer menu item added to help menu of the config tool.
* Remove BBC Backstage EPG grabber which the BBC no longer supports.
* Update the BBC sample channels so that the EPG comes from radiotime.
]]>
</ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>
