<SageTVPlugin>



  <Name>ActiveAspectRatios</Name>

  <Identifier>ActiveAspectRatios</Identifier>

  <Description>Automatically adjusts aspect ratio using information provided by comskip.exe.</Description>

  <Author>tmiranda</Author>



  <CreationDate>2011.05.15</CreationDate>

  <ModificationDate>2015.04.09</ModificationDate>

  <Version beta="false">1.20</Version>



  <Desktop>false</Desktop>



  <Webpage>http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/showthread.php?t=55730</Webpage>



  <Dependency>

    <STV>SageTV7</STV>

    <MinVersion>7.1</MinVersion>

  </Dependency>



  <Dependency>

    <Plugin>sagex-api</Plugin>

    <MinVersion>7.0.23.6</MinVersion>

  </Dependency>



  <PluginType>STVI</PluginType>



  <Package>

    <PackageType>STVI</PackageType>

    <Location>http://dl.bintray.com/opensagetv/sagetv-plugins/ActiveAspectRatios/ActiveAspectRatiosSTVi-1.20.zip</Location>

    <MD5>8C0D69DA6A3472A9FD7DBD718A8BBE67</MD5>

  </Package>



  <STVImport>ActiveAspectRatiosSTVi.stvi</STVImport>



  <Package>

    <PackageType>JAR</PackageType>

    <Location>http://dl.bintray.com/opensagetv/sagetv-plugins/ActiveAspectRatios/ActiveAspectRatios-1.20.zip</Location>

    <MD5>11266782A7551C13F3044A4276BDC0E5</MD5>

  </Package>



  <ReleaseNotes>Version 1.20:

- Added an informational pop-up on the first run warning that comskip.ini must be setup properly.

- Added an option to disable showing current aspect ratio on timeline.

- When displaying the OSD Options Menu give the user the choice to display the AAR Options or go to the default Aspect Ratio Mode sub menu.

- If no ratio information is available then the Aspect Ratio Toggle key will have the default behavior.

- Do not allow user to exclude the channel for an Airing that does not have a channel.

- Fixed a NPE if a non-mpg video was missing an .aspects file.

- Fixed a bug that caused the close button to disappear on the mode mapping menu.

- Fixed a bug that caused the Options menu to be too narrow if the user was not using advanced options in other menus.

- Fixed a bug that would reset aspect ratio to default if show had no aspect ratio information and the user had selected a custom aspect ratio.

- Migrated hosting to bintray.



Version 1.10:

- Migrated to SourceForge.



Version 1.00:

- First public release.



Version 0.04 Beta:

- Added sagex dependency to manifest.

- Fixed bug that caused timeline to show 0 for some shows without aspect ratio information.

- Reduced debug information produced by STVi.



Version 0.03 Beta:

- Fixed bug that caused plugin to ignore default AR Mode.

- Added ability to remove channels from the list of channels with fixed AR Modes.

- Added Aspect listener in various dialogs.

- Various cosmetic changes.



Version 0.02 Beta:

- First forum release.</ReleaseNotes>

</SageTVPlugin>
