<SageTVPlugin>

  <Name>Multi-User Support General</Name>

  <Identifier>multiusersupport</Identifier>

  <Author>tmiranda</Author>

  <CreationDate>2011.02.08</CreationDate>

  <ModificationDate>2015.12.05</ModificationDate>

  <Version beta="true">0.143</Version>

  <Desktop>false</Desktop>



  <Description>Support Plugin for Multi-User Support.</Description>



  <Dependency>

    <STV>SageTV7</STV>

    <MinVersion>7.1</MinVersion>

  </Dependency>



  <Dependency>

    <Plugin>sagex-api</Plugin>

    <MinVersion>7.0.23.6</MinVersion>

  </Dependency>



  <PluginType>Standard</PluginType>



  <ImplementationClass>tmiranda.mus.Plugin</ImplementationClass>



  <Package>

    <PackageType>JAR</PackageType>

    <Location>http://github.com/tmiranda1962/MultiUser/releases/download/v0.143/MultiUserSupport.zip</Location>

    <MD5>E040337C9C95400F44D256AE2BB17194</MD5>

  </Package>



  <ReleaseNotes>Version 0.143:

- Moved hosting from Google Code to GitHub. No functionality change.



Version 0.142:

- Added ability to remove user but preserve Favorites and IsWatched() status.  Thanks to bikesquid.

- Small change to getMediaFilesWithImportPrefix() that will hopefully fix the issue of folder view items not being alphabetized correctly.



Version 0.141

 - Fixes by jpaddock3000 to address DVD playback issues.

 - Fixes by jpaddock3000 to set shows as watched if only a small amount at end is unwatched.



Version 0.140:

- Added support for implementing viewing limits.



Version 0.130:

- Added support for default user profile to use if no user is logged on.

- Added some fixes to try to get DVD playback to resume at proper chapter for each user.



Version 0.121:

- Fixed bug that prevented Favorites from being added.

- Fixed bug that prevented folder grouping from working properly.



Version 0.12:

- Changed behavior so Archive and Don't Like function in the same way as Watched.

- Fixed bug that caused user data to get reset when password was changed.

- Added ability to manually make other plugins compatible with the Multi-User plugin.



Version 0.11:

- Fixed bug introduced in v0.10 that prevented new users from being added.

- Fixed bug that caused Manual records requested by a specific user to show up for all users that had not already initialized the Airing..

- Debug enhancements when in advanced_debug mode.



Version 0.10:

- Enhancements to support delete_at_EOF.



Version 0.09:

- Fixed bug that caused DVD playback position to not be remembered. (May still not work correctly.)

- Changed behavior of SetWatched() and ClearWatched().  Now if all users SetWatched() or ClearWatched() the change is reflected in the core.

- Added infrastructure for multiple simultaneous logons.

- Improved handling of partial recordings and other Objects that are not necessarily an Airing or MediaFile.



Version 0.08:

- Updates for compatibility with Sage 7.1.

- Updated IsFavoriteObject.



Version 0.07:

- Added user debugging information to Plugin.start.

- Added support for controlling if users see newly imported videos.

- If no password is provided to setPassword it will default to the UserID.

- Fixed bug that prevented users from seeing a Favorite added by Admin.

- Fixed bug that may leave user associated with a Favorite that had been removed by the core.

- Fixed bug that prevented loglevel from being changed from some UIs.



Version 0.06:

- Changed logging in User class.

- Fixed bug that would cause logging to revert to WARN.

- Fixed bug that would cause Airings to be marked as Watched prematurely which would allow the Sage core to delete the show before all users had watched it.

- Fixed bug that prevented logging to start properly on SageClients that were running on the Sage server.

</ReleaseNotes>



</SageTVPlugin>
