<SageTVPlugin>



	<Name>Podcast Recorder</Name>



  	<Identifier>podcastrecorderplugin</Identifier>



  	<Description>Podcast Recorder provides the ability to manually record Podcasts or select Podcasts as Favorites and automatically record them.

This plugin provides support only.  To install PodcastRecorder please go to the "UI Mod" section of the plugin manager.</Description>



	<Author>tmiranda</Author>



  	<CreationDate>2010.10.01</CreationDate>



  	<ModificationDate>2011.04.29</ModificationDate>



  	<Version beta="true">0.70</Version>



  	<Desktop>false</Desktop>



	<Dependency>

		<STV>SageTV7</STV>

		<MinVersion>7.1</MinVersion>

	</Dependency>



  	<Dependency>

    		<Plugin>sagex-api</Plugin>

    		<MinVersion>7.0.15.0</MinVersion>

  	</Dependency>



  	<Dependency>

    		<Plugin>ortus-mq</Plugin>

    		<MinVersion>1.0.10</MinVersion>

  	</Dependency>



  	<Dependency>

    		<Plugin>log4j</Plugin>

    		<MinVersion>1.2.15</MinVersion>

  	</Dependency>



	<PluginType>Standard</PluginType>



	<ImplementationClass>tmiranda.podcastrecorder.Plugin</ImplementationClass>



  	<Package>

    		<PackageType>JAR</PackageType>

    		<Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/PodcastRecorder-0.70.zip</Location>

    		<MD5>C5CB327D26EF91112B2C572779C4D135</MD5>

  	</Package>



	<ReleaseNotes>Beta 0.70:

- Added API to manually mark or unmark an Episode as downloaded.

- Try to get Episode title from AiringID, if it's been set.

- Remove redundant database update to improve performance.

- Will now monitor the directory specified in the online options for old files that need to be cleaned up.

- Fixed problem with servialVersionUID that caused database to be invalid for each new release.



Beta 0.60:

- Added ability to record more than the default number of displayed items (usually 20) for Podcasts such as YouTube Channels.

- Start using SetManualRecordProperty() to store metadata.

- Fixed bug that would cause the Favorite status of recorded Episodes to remain the same even though the user changed the Favorite status of the Podcast.

- Fixed bug that prevented MediaFile metadata from getting the correct Favorite status.



Beta 0.50:

- Major overhaul of database routines.

- Fixed bug preventing Channel.Com items from being recorded.

- PodcastKey was not serializable which caused errors when running from a SageClient.

- Added check for downloaded files with 0 length.  Consider this a failed download.

- Added custom Airing metadata for IsPodcast and IsFavoritePodcast.

- Improvements to debugging information.



Beta 0.40:

- Fixed bug that caused excessive memory usage.

- Updated for Sage 7.1.



Beta 0.25:

- Recorded Podcasts now appear as Recordings instead of Imported Videos.

- Fixed a bug that caused the loglevel to reset to "Error".

- Fixed a bug that caused database to continually grow causing Java out of memory errors.

- Changed the way information is stored so that in the future upgrading the plugin will not result in losing all Favorite information.

- Added Configuration option to display advanced settings.

- Added an advanced setting to optionally display a system message if new Favorite Podcasts are available.

- Added an advanced setting to optionally display a system message of Favorite Podcasts have been downloaded.

- Added an advanced setting to allow manual checking for new episodes.

- Added an advanced setting that prints the entire database into the logfile.

- Updated plugin manifest to include dependency on log4j since it is missing from the ortus-mq manifest.

- Improved changing how often scan for new Podcasts occurs.

- Improved the handling of stop() and destroy().

- Improved error handling when sending messages to and from the server.

- Improved error handling if an exception happens while downloading Podcasts.



Beta 0.22 - First public release.</ReleaseNotes>



</SageTVPlugin>
