<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SageTVPlugin>

  <Name>Gemstone for Default SageTV9 (previously Diamond)</Name>
  <Identifier>DiamondSTVi</Identifier>
  <Description>Major update of the Diamond STVi.</Description>
  <Author>JOrton,jusjoken,Fuzzy,EvilPenguin,bialio,PluckyHD</Author>
  <CreationDate>2010.11.01</CreationDate>
  <ModificationDate>2024.11.09</ModificationDate>
  <Version>4.0609</Version>

  <Dependency>
   <Core/>
    <MinVersion>9.1.6.0</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <Dependency>
    <Plugin>phoenix-core</Plugin>
    <MinVersion>3.3.0</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <Dependency>
    <Plugin>googleweather</Plugin>
    <MinVersion>3.1.2</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <Dependency>
   <Plugin>gemstone-api</Plugin>
   <MinVersion>1.0606</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <Dependency>
   <Plugin>gemstone-theme</Plugin>
   <MinVersion>1.0407</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>

  <PluginType>STVI</PluginType>

  <Package>
   <PackageType>STV</PackageType>
   <Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/Gemstone1_0606.zip</Location>
   <MD5>5c19c84f80f5e3531fd229c74ea087b3</MD5>
  </Package>

  <Package>
    <PackageType>STV</PackageType>
    <Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/GemstoneDefaults1_0401.zip</Location>
    <MD5>00775BE716070C5ECD0E2ED4A2378485</MD5>
  </Package>

  <STVImport>GemstonePlugin.stvi</STVImport>

  <ReleaseNotes>
    Version 1.0607 Include OWM 3.0 change by ardyssey
    Version 1.0606 Fix for filters and changes to improve logging
    Version 1.0605 Fix for idle lockups
    Version 1.0604 Fix for weather forecast widgets and added logging for flow filters
    Version 1.0603 Fix for weather backgrounds #2
    Version 1.0602 Fix for weather backgrounds
    Version 1.0601 Changed weather system to use OpenWeatherMap from the updated Google Weather plugin
                   OpenWeatherMap - this requires a developer key.
                    - Sign up at https://home.openweathermap.org/users/sign_up
                    - Create a file in the root SageTV folder called owmkey.properties with only 1 line in it "key=userkey"
                    - no quotes in the line and replace userkey with the one you get when signing up
                    - without a user key Open Weather will not update nor allow locations to be added
    Version 1.0501 Removed Weather Underground and fixed Yahoo Weather
                   Added Dark Sky Weather - this requires a developer key.
                    - Sign up at https://darksky.net/dev
                    - Create a file in the root SageTV folder called darksky.properties with only 1 line in it "key=userkey"
                    - no quotes in the line and replace userkey with the one you get when signing up
                    - without a user key Dark Sky provider will not update other than on restart of the server
    Version 1.0407 Fix for checked and unchecked images
    Version 1.0406 Fix for Android Mini Client image issue
    Version 1.0404 Fix for Windows Client to get weather location from server
    Version 1.0403 Fix for EpisodeSimpleList losing focus after play
    Version 1.0402 Minor change to handle default weather location
    Version 1.0401 Based on SageTV v9.1.7 STV plus various fixes - see forums
    Version 1.0301 Based on SageTV v9 STV
    Version 1.0203 NO CHANGES - just moved the packages to BinTray from Google Code
    Version 1.0201 YouTube Fixes, New/updated Task Switcher and started working on icons for menus
    Version 1.0194 Minor fixes for reported issues
    Version 1.0193 New Dual Flow plus numerous changes/fixes - see forums
    Version 1.0182 Numerous changes/fixes - see forums
    Version 1.0174 Update to include Sage 7.1.9.10 base (YouTube changes)
    Version 1.0173 First Public beta release
    Version 1.017 Numerous changes/fixes - see forums
    Version 1.0162 Fix for menu items loading before init completed
    Version 1.0161 Fix for compatibility issue for other plugins.
    Version 1.016 First Full STV version.  Changes to improve memory footprint.
    Version 1.015 Numerous changes/fixes - see forums
    Version 1.014 Minor changes to support rotated images on the extenders
    Version 1.013 Numerous changes/fixes plus new Weather system based on phoenix core
    Version 1.012 Inline Flow added
    Version 1.011 Metro Menu, TodaysRecordings, Menu Tweak, Stage Reflections, Unselected Flow item transparency option, Weather Icons selection, Banner in Sage Flow
    Version 1.010 Google and Weather.com supported now, new Gemstone Theme, Menu transparency options, Weather forecast Widget details
    Version 1.009 Fixes for Menu Manager shared Menu File
    Version 1.008 Fixes, many menu manager changes, common import/export, 360 fix, Disable for non-compatible plugins, others
    Version 1.007 Fixes, xml location change, adm fix, more configurable items for flows
    Version 1.006 Fixes, memory improvements plus Updates to many Flows and added Fanart and Center Flows
    Version 1.005 Fixes plus Sideways Flow, ADM integrated.
    Version 1.004 Fixes plus optional View Cache.
    Version 1.003 Play options fix and List/Sage Flow updates.
    Version 1.002 Initial test release.
  </ReleaseNotes>

</SageTVPlugin>
