<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SageTVPlugin>
    <Name>Phoenix Core Services</Name>
    <Identifier>phoenix-core</Identifier>
    <Description>
        Phoenix Core Services provides the following services
        * automatic metadata and fanart fetching from external sources such as TheMovieDB, and TVDb.
        * dynamic menus
        * custom views
        * user profiles
        * weather
        * dynamic configuration
    </Description>
    <Author>stuckless,jusjoken,bialio,meinmaui</Author>
    <CreationDate>2010.06.05</CreationDate>
    <ModificationDate>2022.11.08</ModificationDate>
    <ResourcePath>phoenix-core</ResourcePath>
    <Version>3.5.0</Version>

    <Webpage><![CDATA[https://github.com/stuckless/sagetv-phoenix-core]]></Webpage>

    <Dependency>
        <Plugin>phoenix-api</Plugin>
        <MinVersion>3.5.0</MinVersion>
    </Dependency>
    <PluginType>Standard</PluginType>
    <Package>
        <PackageType>System</PackageType>
        <Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/phoenix-core-3.5.0.zip</Location>
        <MD5>23a473f2ce39e643251cc56a00a9ba0e</MD5>
    </Package>
    <ImplementationClass>sagex.phoenix.plugin.PhoenixPlugin</ImplementationClass>
    <ReleaseNotes>
# 3.5.0
* Updated to use the new TVDB V4 provider free of charge thanks to a negotiated license with TheTVDB
# 3.4.3
* Added TMDB as a free TV provider
* Added TVDB V4 as a TV provider - needs a PIN with a subscription to TVDB
* Fix: Old TVDB provider should now work on Java 11
* Fix: if Fanart is disabled (local and central), metadata will still be retrieved unless Automatic  Fanart/Metadata is disabled

# 3.3.1
* Removed weather functionality as all included providers are no longer available
* Weather for Gemstone and SageTV is now handled by the GWeather plugin

# 3.2.3
* Fanart Image fix (redirection not handled correctly)

# 3.2.2
* Weather Fixes
* While each provider can have it's own update check interval, the main API will one as well (configurable) and any attempt to Update() the weather during this interval will be ignored.
* The API will ignore changes that are the same. ie, setting same provider over and over, or setting the same units or locations, etc, will just be ignored, and not passed to the implementation.
* The weather configuration can be "locked" (in BMT Weather Configuration). ie, if you have weather set to Yahoo with a location and units, you can "lock" it so that any API request to change this this will be ignored. I did this mainly because of a bug in Gemstore where it keeps changing my weather provider and units
* SageTV Debugging - Exposed SageTV debugging flags to BMT Web UI (configuration)
 
# 3.2.1
* Fixes to allow failed TV lookups to retry (most failures are "Too many connections")

# 3.2.0
* Rewrote TVDB lookups using TVDB API

# 3.1.0
* Fixed various scraper issues for metadata/fanart (primarily around bluray and dvd)
* Removed HTBackdrops (api/site no longer available)
* Fixed failing JUnit tests

# 3.0.7
* Added Channel Grouper

# 3.0.6
* Fixed Fanart color issues
* Fanart Scaled automatically to max screen size on download
* On Save, will try to fetch fanart, if fanart is missing
* Added Config option to rescale source fanart
* Refactored "timer" code to use common Executors
* Added support for common menu actions to be shared across menus


# 3.0.4
* Fixed possible plugin deadlock when using SageTVEventBus

# 3.0.3
* Added support for font icon mappings

# 3.0.2
* Xml Validation will not completely fail if there are missing views, filters, sources, etc.  It will continue to load the views and flag the views with errors.
* Fixed bug where WeatherAPI was generating with compile errors.
    </ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>