<SageTVPlugin>
	<Name>twiederTweaks</Name>
	<Identifier>twiedertweaks</Identifier>
	<Description>A collection of SageTV7 UI tweaks
This is a collection of SageTV7 interface tweaks:
GLOBAL:
 * Added the disk-usage bar to the bottom of the screen
RECORDINGS
 * Removed the "REC" indicator next to active recordings, moving remaining indicators to the right (for more title/episode space)
 * Added red background to listings for currently active recordings
 * Offset the episode name
 * Added a configurable date to the right of the episode name
 * Removed the numbering in the right panel for group recordings
 * Made watched episode names font configurable in right panel for group recordings
 * Made unwatched episode names font configurable in right panel for group recordings
 * Added a configurable date next to the episode name in the right panel for group recordings
 * Displays Season and Episode numbers in details
 * Can display Season/Episode number instead of dates (listed above)

This is a work-in-progess. Let me know if you like these tweaks, or what changes you would appreciate

</Description>
	<Author>twieder</Author>
	<CreationDate>2010-05-25</CreationDate>
	<ModificationDate>2010-06-01</ModificationDate>
	<Version>0.7.5</Version>
	<PluginType>STVI</PluginType>
	<STVImport>twiederTweaks.stvi</STVImport>
	<Dependency>
		<Plugin>bmt</Plugin>
	</Dependency>
		<Dependency>
		<Plugin>sageortus-api</Plugin>
		<MinVersion>1.0</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>
	<Dependency>
		<STV>SageTV7</STV>
		<MinVersion>7.0</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>
	<ReleaseNotes>v0.6.5 - Added setup menu item.
		Watched and Unwatched font styles and alpha are now configurable for right-side episode lists
		Date source (Original, Airing or none) is configureable for both main listings and episode listings

v0.7.0
	Season/Episode now an option instead of date *
	Season and Episode number displayed in listing and detail pages *
		* note - these depend on BMT to get this information

v0.7.5
	Right panel sort is now working
	Right panel scrolling bug fixed
	Recording color border removed
	</ReleaseNotes>
	<Package>
		<PackageType>STVI</PackageType>
		<Location>http://www.wallofcats.com/sagetv/twiederTweaks_0.7.5.zip</Location>
		<MD5>3FD046FF7FF7B72250B195DF18CCF5E0</MD5>
	</Package>
</SageTVPlugin>
