<SageTVPlugin>
 <Name>Complementary Metadata Tools (CMT)</Name>
 <Identifier>CMT</Identifier>
 <Description>Provides the ability to edit metadata within SageTV and fetch and manage metadata and fanart.
 Displays and saves information from the Internet Movie Data Base.
 Provides access to BMT configuration, scanning and lookups from within SageTV.
 Can create .my and .properties files for recordings, cleanup orphan .my and .properties files and import information from .my files into the SageTV wiz.bin.
 Provides the ability to display information from .my files in Recording and Video Detail panels.
 ***** THIS PLUGIN REPLACES "Read, Write and Edit Metadata" and "IMDB Search" plugins in SageTV 7.1</Description>
 <Author>JREkiwi</Author>
 <CreationDate>2011.04.02</CreationDate>
 <ModificationDate>2021.03.13</ModificationDate>
 <Version>3.1.9</Version>
 <Desktop>false</Desktop>
 <Dependency>
  <STV>SageTV7</STV>
  <MinVersion>7.1</MinVersion>
 </Dependency>
 <Dependency>
  <JVM></JVM>
  <MinVersion>1.8</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>
 <Dependency>
  <Plugin>df_sageutils</Plugin>
  <MinVersion>1.0</MinVersion>
 </Dependency>
 <Dependency>
  <Plugin>sageutls</Plugin>
  <MinVersion>1.4.2</MinVersion>
 </Dependency>
  <Dependency>
   <Plugin>phoenix-api</Plugin>
   <MinVersion>2.5.13</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>
  <Dependency>
   <Plugin>phoenix-core</Plugin>
  <MinVersion>2.5.13</MinVersion>
 </Dependency>
 <Dependency>
  <Plugin>nielm_sageimdb</Plugin>
  <MinVersion>2.0.4</MinVersion>
 </Dependency>
<Webpage>https://forums.sagetv.com/forums/showthread.php?t=49360</Webpage>
<PluginType>STVI</PluginType>
 <Package>
   <PackageType>STVI</PackageType>
   <Location>https://github.com/JREkiwi/SageTVPlugins/releases/download/CMT_3.1.9/CMT_3.1.9.zip</Location>
   <MD5>45D4C71FAE6482E4F1E2C857E91BC56A</MD5>
 </Package>
<STVImport>CMT.stvi</STVImport>
<ReleaseNotes>3.1.9
New version of nielm_sageimdb
Remove Trailer Search that hasn't worked for years
3.1.8.2
New version of nielm_sageimdb

3.1.8.1
Change download to https

3.1.8
Reinstate Season and Epsiode numbers on Program for display and save
Reinstate Birth Info on Person
Add Death Info on Person
Fix multiple nicknames

3.1.7.1
New manifest for updated niem_sageimdb

3.1.7
Changes to library scanning to reduce impact
New nielm_sageimdb thanks spencerw

3.1.6
Change from using UserRecords as the WIZ.BIN impact didn't justify the benefit. Will cause a temporary increase in WIZ.BIN size that will reduce.
Fix changing recordings to videos when enable_converting_imported_videos_to_tv_recordings is enabled
Added ability to set Season and Episode Number if not already set when changing videos to recordings

3.1.5
Cleanup user records from WIZ.BIN for files that have been deleted.  May cause a temporary increase in WIZ.BIN size, but size will reduce following the next restart or EPG update

3.1.4
Force removal of old IMDB Search plugin
Fix Options and OK not working in some configurations

3.1.3
Change dependencies for new IMDB JAR
Change default Online Video Search to YouTube
Fix issue with occasionally grabbing the wrong title for IMDB search when playing a video

3.1.2
Change dependencies for new IMDB JAR
Reinstate IMDB person Filomographies as they are mostly working

3.1.1
Change dependencies for new IMDB JAR
Temporarily remove IMDB person Filomographies as they don't work yet

3.1.0
Change IMDB Trailers to use YouTube
Add Move Imported Videos to Recordings
Add Move Group of Imported Videos to Recordings
Add Move Recording to Imported Videos

3.0.8
Change dependencies for new IMDB JAR
Tweaks for Gemstone

3.0.7
Add IMDB Goofs
Change manifest for updated IMDB JAR file

3.0.6
Fix reflections in Edit Metadata
Add support for phoenix music backgrounds

3.0.5
Changes to common code for Fanart scaling

3.0.4
Added viewing/deleting of thumbnails
Fixes for some changes in IMDB Trivia and Quotes format
Change person search to handle roles appended to persons name
Changes for changed usage of Title and Episode fields for imported videos in SageTV 7.1.8

3.0.3
Add saving Original Air Date from IMDB
Fix null exceptions when processing IMDB Trivia

3.0.2
Fix exception when running BMT type scans on UNC directory paths
Change .properties file creation to produce a file containing ALL properties
Change timing of automatic .properties file creation to allow for BMT etc to fetch info first
Change .properties overwrite control to use AddUserRecord to maintain written status
Add detection of Diamond plugin for Global use of background and thumbnail handling
Add background processing shared by Phoenix Fanart and Upcoming Movies

3.0.0
Merge of RW Metadata and IMDB Search imports
Add Phoenix image scaling
Setup for change in usage of GetShowTitle() and GetShowEpisode() for future API changes in SageTV 7.1
</ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>
