<SageTVPlugin>
 <Name>Comskip Playback</Name>
 <Identifier>ComskipPlayback</Identifier>
 <Description>Adds support for reading the edl or txt files generated by comskip or showanalyzer and skipping commercial breaks during playback
 This plugin is the continuation of the original work by at least malore, nielm, flachbar, sundansx and razrsharpe</Description>
 <Author>JREkiwi</Author>
 <CreationDate>2007.01.17</CreationDate>
 <ModificationDate>2021.03.13</ModificationDate>
 <Version>2.1.3.3</Version>
 <Desktop>false</Desktop>
 <Dependency>
<STV>SageTV7</STV>
<MinVersion>7.0</MinVersion>
</Dependency>
 <Dependency>
  <JVM></JVM>
  <MinVersion>1.8</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>
 <Webpage>http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/showthread.php?t=48408</Webpage>
<PluginType>STVI</PluginType>
 <Package>
   <PackageType>STVI</PackageType>
   <Location>https://github.com/JREkiwi/ComskipPlayback/releases/download/2.1.3/Comskip_Playback_2.1.3.zip</Location>
   <MD5>7C1CEC0E9EF447821EED78D649B78858</MD5>
 </Package>
 <Package>
   <PackageType>STVI</PackageType>
   <Location>https://github.com/JREkiwi/ComskipPlayback/releases/download/2.1.3/Comskip_Playback_Sample.zip</Location>
   <MD5>C7530AA2A8731C2954E0B529811B8B9B</MD5>
   <Overwrite>false</Overwrite>
 </Package>
<STVImport>Comskip_Playback.stvi</STVImport>
<ReleaseNotes>2.1.3.3
Change download to GitHub
2.1.3.2
Change download to https

2.1.3.1
Change download location

2.1.3
Change to delete comskip files for all file segments
Change to allow Run Comskip button for all video types

2.1.2
Change to using java.IO.file to take advantage of Core path separator handling.  Thanks Narflex

2.1.1
Work around linux pathing issues.  Thanks stuckless for the docker image.

2.1.0.2
Change Bintray to use http instead of https

2.1.0.1
Move download to BinTray

2.1.0
Change to using SageTV API calls to read comskip files.  Eliminate the need to have clients match recording directory paths. Thanks Fuzzy

2.0.15
Change to support edl_skip_field=3 in comskip.ini for support of XBMC skipping.  This plugin treats 0 and 3 as a skip

2.0.14
Fix Autoskip thread shutting down when using options panels when playing mediafile
Changed Loop wait time for delayed skipping

2.0.13
Rework autoskip thread startup and shutdown to prevent multiple threads running
Remove REW disabling autoskip as it introduced lots of issues.  However Autoskip was changed to not skip when REW back into the end of a commercial block
Change autoskip disable on left arrow to be a minimum of 30 secs as some Transport Stream files would have jumps in the timeline greater than the 12sec minimum, so wouldn't autoskip
Rename all variables to remove possibilty of conflicts with other plugins

2.0.12
Fix Autoskip not working consistently on SageTV clients

2.0.11
Add skip delay adjustments to Media Player Options Menu
Fix autoskip not working after using left arrow or left skip buttons when debug logging was not enabled

2.0.10
Change Disable Timeline Scaling to set value in UI properties file

2.0.9
Fix timebar under malore preview and lists
Add options for timebars in malore menus - under preview, under description
Fix displaying timebar on imported video detail when there is no comskip files

2.0.8
Reinstate configurable autoskip temporary disable time

2.0.7
Reworked disabling autoskip on Left, REW etc. and made disabling autoskip on REW optional in Operation Options
Relocated timebars as they were breaking the autosizing of the shadow area behind previews etc.
Changed skip delay settings to use and adjustable value by default.  Manual value entering is also still available
Changed default for Start on Watch to not overwrite an existing .edl file

2.0.6
Added disabling autoskip on REW, REW2, FWD, FWD2
Added configurable autoskip disable time when manually skipping

2.0.5
Fix marker icons on malore view
Change themed values loading
2.0.4
Adjusted size and location of timebar displays

2.0.3
Added optional timebar displays in detail and list panels
Added more options for selecting where Comskip icons are displayed
Reworked options menu to cater for new timebar and icon options
2.0.2
Fix height of Commercial Markers in Timebar
Theme colors and alpha of Commercial Timebar Markers
2.0.1
Fix timebar not showing on skip
Change default setting for manual Comskip button visibility
Change manifest to remove Desktop only

2.0.0
Complete port of old Comskip Playback import
Added option for disabling timeline scaling on skip

1.5.4.2
Fix Capitalization of STVi so the manifest and file match (compatibility with linux users)

1.5.4.1
Removed dependency on GKusnickTools

1.5.4
Inital V7 Port
Working Sections: changes to the OSD timeline, functionality during playback (autoskip, left/right to skip), and Comskip Options on the OSD and under Detailed Setup -> Customize.

Not Working: Anything else, ie the EPG and info views were not relinked.</ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>
