<SageTVPlugin>
 <Name>Multi Function Stop</Name>
 <Identifier>MultiFunctionStop</Identifier>
 <Description>Presents a panel with multiple options available when Stop is used on recordings, videos and DVDs. Options include Resume, Restart, Delete (with options) and goto Main Menu.
  Adds an option to close a mediafile when playback is complete.
  Adds a restart option to the Delete/Don't Delete panel presented at the end of playback of a recording.
  This is a port of nielm's Multi Function Stop for the Default STV.</Description>
 <Author>JREkiwi</Author>
 <CreationDate>2005.05.31</CreationDate>
 <ModificationDate>2021.03.13</ModificationDate>
 <Version>1.9.6.2</Version>
 <Desktop>false</Desktop>
 <Webpage>http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/showthread.php?t=48999</Webpage>
 <Dependency>
  <STV>SageTV7</STV>
  <MinVersion>7.0</MinVersion>
 </Dependency>
 <Dependency>
  <JVM></JVM>
  <MinVersion>1.8</MinVersion>
  </Dependency>
<PluginType>STVI</PluginType>
 <Package>
   <PackageType>STVI</PackageType>
   <Location>https://github.com/JREkiwi/MultiFunctionStop/releases/download/1.9.6/Multi_Function_Stop_1.9.6.zip</Location>
   <MD5>F1B638F350E4C7C2F48782A8D67210EC</MD5>
 </Package>
<STVImport>Multi_Function_Stop.stvi</STVImport>
<ReleaseNotes>1.9.6.1
Change download to GitHub
1.9.6.1
Change download to https

1.9.6
Added Option to disable Mutifunction Stop and have Close Media File Enabled

1.9.5
Remove duplicate code from listeners
Rework Restart Playback as it wouldn't work at the end of a mediafile if Close Media was enabled
Rework Close Media to only run if a Media File was still loaded

1.9.4
Reworked setting of Watched etc state when deleting on stop and when doing standard delete as the status more often than not was not getting set
Added Delete and Set Watched to standard delete options from recordings like ShadeBlue's Delete and Set Watched import

1.9.3
Reworked "Cancel Recording, Set Watched and Delete" to retry the delete in the background. Previously, when the file was in use by something like comskip the delete would fail.

1.9.2
Fixed compatability issues with Auto Aspect Switcher plugin

1.9.1
Added 1.9 changes to the correct base file

1.9
Fixed audio playing on Main Menu when it shouldn't
Added restart on EOF deletion panel
Change to have delete available on archived recordings
Change to have delete not visible on videos when allow deletion of videos is disabled

1.8
Added Cancel recording - Set Watched and Delete
Added Delete option for imported videos
Added Option to Close Media File when playback is finished (SageMC behaviour)

1.7
Added more options on delete (Delete and Set Watched etc)

1.6
Port of nielm's Multi Function Stop import
Enabled theming of panel icons
</ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>
