<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SageTVPlugin>
	<Name>Batch Metadata Tools - Web Interface</Name>
	<Identifier>bmtweb</Identifier>
	<Description>
Web Interface for Batch Metadata Tools, commonly referred
to as bmt. The web interface enables you to do edit metadata manually
from a web browser. In addition to simple editing of metadata, bmt is
build on the Phoenix APIs, and it provides a web interface to the
Phoenix Views. ie, It allows you to browser your media collection from
the web web browser. While browsing your collection you can also find
metadata and fanart for a group of media files, or for a single item.
		
BMT also provides a number of other batch tools for cleaning up metadata, or
performing some common operations.  Some of these include; Exporting a
.properties for some or all mediafiles; Cleaning up Genres; Setting the
watched status on files, etc
	</Description>
	<Screenshot><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=9772&stc=1&d=1266629522]]></Screenshot>
	<Author>stuckless</Author>
	<CreationDate>2008.07.19</CreationDate>
	<ModificationDate>2016.09.11</ModificationDate>
	<Version>4.100.0</Version>
	<Desktop>false</Desktop>
	<ResourcePath>plugins/bmtweb</ResourcePath>
	<Webpage><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=46]]></Webpage>

	<Dependency>
		<Plugin>Jetty</Plugin>
		<MinVersion>1.7</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<Dependency>
		<Plugin>phoenix-core</Plugin>
		<MinVersion>2.3.47</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<Dependency>
		<Plugin>javax-validation-api</Plugin>
		<MinVersion>1.1.0</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<Dependency>
		<Core/>
		<MinVersion>9.0.7</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<PluginType>Standard</PluginType>

	<Package>
		<PackageType>System</PackageType>
		<Location>http://dl.bintray.com/opensagetv/sagetv-plugins/bmtweb/4.100.0/bmtweb-war-4.100.0.zip</Location>
		<MD5>3a777756eaae470a03840004679dfe99</MD5>
	</Package>

	<!-- context file must be installed after the war file -->
	<Package>
		<PackageType>System</PackageType>
		<Location>http://dl.bintray.com/opensagetv/sagetv-plugins/bmtweb/4.100.0/bmtweb-context-4.100.0.zip</Location>
		<MD5>d02d619d3f56697c4c23ed01263a8189</MD5>
	</Package>
	<ReleaseNotes>
4.10
* Added code to automatically download the x-vfs.xml (Phoenix vfs file) if it is missing
* Movie BMT views from the Phoenix vfs file to the bmt.xml vfs file
* Fixed missing BatchOperation dependency on "allvideos"
* Fixed Export Thumbnail issue (was creating 16x16 black images)
* Removed Batch Operations from the Tools Menu (you should use them from a view using Batch Operations)

4.9.21
* Increased field sizes for description and titles
* Added link to imdb
* Added Xml Editor for editing VFS and Menus
* Added icon to the Views to show/hide views
* Added icon to the Views to quickly add a view as a menu

4.9.20
* Added Previous/Next and "Save and Next" to the Metadata Editor panels
* Added File path to the MediaTitles dialog 
* Browser view resets to the top when you select a view or navigate a folder
* New fanart configuration panel
* New Tabebed Metadata Editor panel
* Refresh has menu of items that can be refreshed
* Refreshing configurations now give an indication of the error

4.9.15
* Search box will now treat 1 and 2 word searches as Title search.
* Search box will now accept "Enter" to invoke search
* Added simple help icon/dialog for the new PQL Search
* Fixed bug in FileChooser that would not let you choose a directory that was empty
* PQL Search is not cleared when it fails
* Reset the batch operations list after each operation

4.9.14
* Added Year to upcoming movies
* Changed the Search to use PQL so that you can do advanced searches using the search bar
* Batch Updater now supports +Genre or -Genre to add or remove a specific Genre
* Verified that Batch Import As Recording does work

4.9.13
* Fixed display issue with runtime 

4.9.12
* Added Batch Metadata Editor (can now batch edit multiple files)
* Added RAW Metadata Editor to edit any Metadata field for a media item
* Can download series only fanart
* Fixed fanart download bug for manual fanart
* Can enter runtime as '### mins' and shows runtime in minutes
* Original Air Date now shows hh:mm
* Can enter Original Air Date as a number or 'YYYY-MM-DD HH:MM'
* Hides the view panel when editing metadata
* Basic 'back' button navigation when in the Edit Metadata panel
* Configuration Help now shows more information in the help dialog.
* Fixed bug with support request generator that prevented it from created support requests
* Home Videos now correctly uses semi-colon instead of comma
* Home Videos now uses case insensitive paths
* Fixed bug where genres was not using the new Sage7 / separator.  Genres will now use /
* Added "Add File Matcher" from the metadata editor panel to quickly add an entry to the MediaTitles.xml 

4.9.11
* Minor enhancements to Airing type items
* Added simple Airing viewer
* Can update fanart on Airings
* Can issue Manual Record on Airing
* Can toggle watched status on media files and Airings
* Minor ui tweaks

4.9.10
* Can change view categories
* Added press and hold on video item, with options to delete or view generated thumbnails of video
* Auto retry for failed metadata lookups (in phoenix-core, but listing it here as well)

4.9.8
* added plugin viewer (configuration -> SageTV Plugins)
* minor changes required for the newer 2.3.14 phoenix.jar

4.9.7
* fixed bug where the first time dialog would always show
* added watched icon to the media file
* added play icon to the media file (with play on client dialog)
* fixed bug where bmt would overwrite metadata even if preserve metadata was enabled
* Added Fanart caching to help when fanart hosted on servers
* Added support for a null transform to allow the image apis to cache files without transforming them

4.9.6
*	262	 WebUI: Scrolling handled by browser window   BMTWEB BMT	 
*	263	 WebUI: Notifications are handled by notification manager   BMTWEB BMT	 
*	265	 WebUI: Can't update Movie Title   BMTWEB BMT	 
*	266	 Fix SageAiring-NoEpisode scraper   Phoenix	 
*	267	 Add Movie.Year scraper   Phoenix	 
*	269	 Ability to set a default poster   BMTWEB BMT	 
*	270	 Some Movies showing S00E00   BMT	 
*	274	 Refresh MediaTitles broken from the web ui   BMTWEB BMT	 
*	276	 First time dialog shows every time   BMTWEB BMT	 
*	277	 Title Scraping Tweaks   BMT

4.9.5
* Fixed Sage Imports View
* Added Fanart Refresh
* Exclude Filter now works in Missing Metadata View
* Added Batch Operation to remove Year from Show Metadata
* Added Manual TV Lookup by Date
* Can edit genres from the web ui

4.9.4
* Fixed 'Discover Defaults' so that it works better with wildly named files.
* TV Show Title can now be updated
* Added ExternalID checks so that field should never be null.  (ie, it should be populated)

4.9.3
* Added Batch tools to clean up titles (ie, either adding relative path or removing relative path)
* Fixed Search Dialog on Find Metadata (numerous issues; it should not discover, search, and update correctly)
* Added TV Series Info Id and VFS Id fields to the metadata view

4.9.2
* Minor update to add compatibility to a sagex-api change
 
4.9.1
* Minor update that includes the ability to
enable/disable channels
(Configuration -> Channels)

4.9
* Fixed bug in TV
Scanner that caused some items to fail to be scanned
correctly from the
web ui
* Fixed Group by Genres View
* Fxied 'Movies' view to be
'Recorded Movies'
* Added Batch Operations for generating .properties,
generating
thumbnails, and for fixing genres.
	</ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>
