<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SageTVPlugin>
	<Name>Batch Metadata Tools - Web Interface</Name>
	<Identifier>bmtweb</Identifier>
	<Description>
Web Interface for Batch Metadata Tools, commonly referred
to as bmt. The web interface enables you to do edit metadata manually
from a web browser. In addition to simple editing of metadata, bmt is
build on the Phoenix APIs, and it provides a web interface to the
Phoenix Views. ie, It allows you to browser your media collection from
the web web browser. While browsing your collection you can also find
metadata and fanart for a group of media files, or for a single item.
		
BMT also provides a number of other batch tools for cleaning up metadata, or
performing some common operations.  Some of these include; Exporting a
.properties for some or all mediafiles; Cleaning up Genres; Setting the
watched status on files, etc
	</Description>
	<Screenshot><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=9772&stc=1&d=1266629522]]></Screenshot>
	<Author>stuckless</Author>
	<CreationDate>2008.07.19</CreationDate>
	<ModificationDate>2022.11.08</ModificationDate>
	<Version>4.501.0</Version>
	<Desktop>false</Desktop>
	<ResourcePath>plugins/bmtweb</ResourcePath>
	<Webpage><![CDATA[http://forums.sagetv.com/forums/forumdisplay.php?f=46]]></Webpage>

	<Dependency>
		<Plugin>Jetty</Plugin>
		<MinVersion>3.0.1</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<Dependency>
		<Plugin>phoenix-core</Plugin>
		<MinVersion>3.5.0</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<Dependency>
		<Plugin>javax-validation-api</Plugin>
		<MinVersion>1.1.0</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<Dependency>
		<Core/>
		<MinVersion>9.0.7</MinVersion>
	</Dependency>

	<PluginType>Standard</PluginType>

	<Package>
		<PackageType>System</PackageType>
		<Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/bmtweb-war-4.501.0.zip
		</Location>
		<MD5>b4cb2ed1a84a5f7ee4c57095c5316c5a</MD5>
	</Package>

	<!-- context file must be installed after the war file -->
	<Package>
		<PackageType>System</PackageType>
		<Location>https://github.com/OpenSageTV/sagetv-plugin-repo/releases/download/1/bmtweb-config-4.501.0.zip
		</Location>
		<MD5>803b73e6067c1f9a99de10cef1053b33</MD5>
	</Package>
	<ReleaseNotes>
4.501.0
* Updated to use the new TVDB V4 provider free of charge thanks to a negotiated license with TheTVDB
4.403.0
* Updated to allow TMDB as a TV provider and added the new TVDB V4 provider (needs a subscription to use)
4.300.0
* Updated for jetty 9 and changes for TMDB to handle TV
4.100.0
* Updated for SageTV V9
* Fixed Search so that it does a title contains search by default
* Fixed Add Matcher so that it works with () and so that it cleans up older entries with same ID.  	
	</ReleaseNotes>
</SageTVPlugin>
